PAFF：Wake up~Can you hear me?
PAFF：醒醒，听得见我吗？
PAFF：It's already been three months since everything happened.
PAFF：那之后已经过了三个月了，你过得如何？
Leo：From the bottom of our hearts, we promise that from here on out,
PAFF：在解除了 Vanessa 对世界造成的危机后
PAFF：After averting the crisis that Vanessa threatened the world with...
Leo：敝社承诺今后将不会再祕密地使用古文明科技
PAFF：A.R.C. abolished the Library's facilities
PAFF：A.R.C. 将 Library 的设施废止
Leo：and will be transparent with all the content of our research
Leo：并会公开透明化所有研究内容
PAFF：and used other types of server technology to replace the operations of the virtual internet
PAFF：并使用其他伺服器技术取代精神网路的营运
Leo：Starting from today, we will implement serious changes to our internal structure
Leo：今后敝社将会进行内部改革
Leo：For the development of society and humanity
Leo：为了社会与人类的发展
PAFF：Of course, many people are unable to accept such a decision
PAFF：当然有许多人无法接受
Leo：we will seriously reconsider our position in society and the direction we are headed...
Leo：重新思考我们的定位和方向……
PAFF：Especially those who lost their loved ones as a result of what happened
PAFF：尤其是因为这次事件失去心爱之人的人们
PAFF：But after a period of time most people returned to their normal lives
PAFF：不过大部份的人仍在一段时间后恢復了原本正常的生活
PAFF：Time gradually diluted all that had occurred...
PAFF：时间也渐渐冲淡这一切……
PAFF：After graduating from university, NEKO became a professional streamer musician
PAFF：NEKO 在从学院毕业后成为了职业的编曲实况主
PAFF：Besides her normal content of music, games and random gossip
PAFF：内容除了熟悉的音乐、游戏与八卦
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Yo-ho! NEKO's here!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：唷嗬！NEKO 登场！
PAFF：she also started a new series
PAFF：她也开设了新的系列节目
PAFF：where she actively goes out to help the victims that were affected by the incident with Vanessa
PAFF：主动关心且帮助那些因 Vanessa 事件而受到伤害的人们
Victim：We don't need help from you internet addicts. Please, go away...
受害者：我们不需要你们这些网路成瘾者的帮助，请回吧……
PAFF：It's not easy, but she doesn't get discouraged
PAFF：过程虽然很辛苦，但她没有气馁
PAFF：She used money she made from her music and streams to set up a foundation
PAFF：用音乐与直播赚的钱也成立了基金会
PAFF：that donates to the people affected and related illnesses
PAFF：对相关人士以及病症进行捐献
PAFF：At night, she's still a die-hard music fan
PAFF：这样的她，夜晚仍然是个单纯的音乐迷
PAFF：As for Xenon, he got back to performing with a band after everything was over
PAFF：Xenon 在那之后也重启了乐团活动
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Not bad~!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：辛苦啦～！
PAFF：Xenon's sister Shannon,
PAFF：Xenon 的妹妹 Shannon
PAFF：she gradually shed the effect that the virtual internet had on her
PAFF：在那之后似乎渐渐脱离了精神网路的影响
PAFF：and her condition started to improve
PAFF：病情也开始好转
PAFF：A.R.C. kept begging Xenon to return
PAFF：A.R.C. 不断恳求 Xenon 回去
PAFF：But no matter how generous their offers were, no matter what position they promised
PAFF：然而，不管他们提供了多麽优渥的待遇与职位
PAFF：Xenon refused to accept
PAFF：Xenon 始终没有答应
PAFF：Perhaps in his heart,
PAFF：也许他心中，有着太多不放下就无法前进的过去吧
PAFF：After the dissolution of Baro,
PAFF：在 Baro 帮瓦解后，JOE 的酒吧在圈内的地位越来越高
PAFF：JOE became more and more like Uncle Saxon
PAFF：JOE 也越来越有舅舅 Saxon 的样子了
PAFF：and some familiar faces could be seen hanging around, just like before
PAFF：店裡也一如往常能见到一些熟面孔
PAFF：Mr. Neumann decided to move to Node 13,
PAFF：Neumann 先生决定移居到 Node 13
PAFF：continuing to research the unsolved mysteries of his ancestors with Sasha
PAFF：与 Sasha 继续研究自己祖先历史中未解的谜团
PAFF：Humanity's interest in ancient technology didn't disappear
PAFF：人类对古文明科技的好奇仍然没有消失
PAFF：and missions of A.R.C.'s Exploration Team continued
PAFF：A.R.C. 探勘队的任务也还在持续中
PAFF：Occasionally, they run into someone with motives different from their own
PAFF：过程中偶尔也会遇到一些目的不同的人
ConneR：Oh? You again?
ConneR：什么？是你呀？
ConneR：Keep up the hard work
ConneR：真是辛苦了
PAFF：Rin was able to break free of A.R.C.'s control,
PAFF：Rin 脱离了 A.R.C. 的控制
PAFF：concealing her Architect identity and living with Sagar
PAFF：并隐藏了自己建造者的身份，与 Sagar 生活在一起
PAFF：She also returned to Node 03 to look for her past memories
PAFF：她也回到 Node 03 寻找自己过去的回忆
Rin：Ah! Oh...
Rin：呀！啊……
Rin：I'm s-so sorry!
Rin：非、非常对不起！
Rin：Wah!
Rin：哇！
Daigo：Chief, here's the part you asked for
Daigo：组长，您要的零件在这裡
PAFF：Last time we heard from Nora
PAFF：最后一次收到 Nora 的消息时
Nora：Thank you, just put it there
Nora：谢谢，放在那边就好
PAFF：she was just about finished repairing ROBO_Head
PAFF：她好像快将 ROBO_Head 修好了
Nora："NORA"
Nora：「NORA」
PAFF：Then... there's me
PAFF：然后……是我
PAFF：Once again, I returned to the stage as PAFF as well as doing performances on the street
PAFF：我，再次以 PAFF 的身份回到了舞台与街上献唱
PAFF：I accepted the fact that I was both Aroma and Kaori...
PAFF：接受了自己同时身为 Aroma，也身为 Kaori 的身份……
PAFF：We... are PAFF
PAFF：PAFF，就是我们
PAFF：Though I don't know what the future holds for humanity now that Vanessa is gone
PAFF：虽然不知道在 Vanessa 消失后，人类的未来将会如何
PAFF：we're going to continue to use music to give power and courage to everyone
PAFF：我们会用音乐继续将力量与勇气带给大家
PAFF：It may not be much
PAFF：也许只有一点点
PAFF：but we'll try to use everything in our power to change this world,
PAFF：但我们也会尝试用自己的全力去改变这个世界
PAFF：because that's all we can do
PAFF：因为这是我们唯一能做的
PAFF：This... is our story.
PAFF：这，就是我们的故事